{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggY29kaW5nIGxhbmd1YWdlIHdhcyB0aGUgIzEgcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2UgaW4gdGVybXMgb2YgdXNhZ2Ugb24gR2l0SHViIGluIDIwMTU/",
            "correct_answer": "SmF2YVNjcmlwdA==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "QyM=",
                "UHl0aG9u",
                "UEhQ"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "VW5peCBUaW1lIGlzIGRlZmluZWQgYXMgdGhlIG51bWJlciBvZiBzZWNvbmRzIHRoYXQgaGF2ZSBlbGFwc2VkIHNpbmNlIHdoZW4/",
            "correct_answer": "TWlkbmlnaHQsIEphbnVhcnkgMSwgMTk3MA==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "TWlkbmlnaHQsIEp1bHkgNCwgMTk3Ng==",
                "TWlkbmlnaHQgb24gdGhlIGNyZWF0b3Igb2YgVW5peCdzIGJpcnRoZGF5",
                "TWlkbmlnaHQsIEp1bHkgNCwgMTk4MA=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzIFJBSUQgc3RhbmQgZm9yPw==",
            "correct_answer": "UmVkdW5kYW50IEFycmF5IG9mIEluZGVwZW5kZW50IERpc2tz",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "UmFwaWQgQWNjZXNzIGZvciBJbmRleGVkIERldmljZXM=",
                "UmFuZ2Ugb2YgQXBwbGljYXRpb25zIHdpdGggSWRlbnRpY2FsIERlc2lnbnM=",
                "UmFuZG9taXplZCBBYnN0cmFjdCBJZGVudGlmaWNhdGlvbiBEZXNjcmlwdGlvbg=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "SW4gSFRNTCwgd2hpY2ggbm9uLXN0YW5kYXJkIHRhZyB1c2VkIHRvIGJlIGJlIHVzZWQgdG8gbWFrZSBlbGVtZW50cyBzY3JvbGwgYWNyb3NzIHRoZSB2aWV3cG9ydD8=",
            "correct_answer": "PG1hcnF1ZWU+PC9tYXJxdWVlPg==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "PHNjcm9sbD48L3Njcm9sbD4=",
                "PG1vdmU+PC9tb3ZlPg==",
                "PHNsaWRlPjwvc2xpZGU+"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb3BlcmF0aW5nIHN5c3RlbSB3YXMgcmVsZWFzZWQgZmlyc3Q/",
            "correct_answer": "TWFjIE9T",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "V2luZG93cw==",
                "TGludXg=",
                "T1MvMg=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbWFpbiBDUFUgaXMgdGhlIFNlZ2EgTWVnYSBEcml2ZSAvIFNlZ2EgR2VuZXNpcz8=",
            "correct_answer": "TW90b3JvbGEgNjgwMDA=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Wmlsb2cgWjgw",
                "WWFtYWhhIFlNMjYxMg==",
                "SW50ZWwgODA4OA=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgaXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgZm9yIHRoZSBmYWlsZWQga2V5IGVzY3JvdyBkZXZpY2UgaW50cm9kdWNlZCBieSB0aGUgTmF0aW9uYWwgU2VjdXJpdHkgQWdlbmN5IGluIDE5OTM/",
            "correct_answer": "Q2xpcHBlciBDaGlw",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "RW5pZ21hIE1hY2hpbmU=",
                "U2tpcGphY2s=",
                "TmF1dGlsdXM="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "LmF0IGlzIHRoZSB0b3AtbGV2ZWwgZG9tYWluIGZvciB3aGF0IGNvdW50cnk/",
            "correct_answer": "QXVzdHJpYQ==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "QXJnZW50aW5h",
                "QXVzdHJhbGlh",
                "QW5nb2xh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "TGFzZXJqZXQgYW5kIGlua2pldCBwcmludGVycyBhcmUgYm90aCBleGFtcGxlcyBvZiB3aGF0IHR5cGUgb2YgcHJpbnRlcj8=",
            "correct_answer": "Tm9uLWltcGFjdCBwcmludGVy",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "SW1wYWN0IHByaW50ZXI=",
                "RGFpc3l3aGVlbCBwcmludGVy",
                "RG90IG1hdHJpeCBwcmludGVy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbmFtZSBvZiB0aGUgZGVmYXVsdCB0aGVtZSB0aGF0IGlzIGluc3RhbGxlZCB3aXRoIFdpbmRvd3MgWFA/",
            "correct_answer": "THVuYQ==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "TmVwdHVuZQ==",
                "V2hpc3RsZXI=",
                "Qmxpc3M="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "SW4gcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcsIHRoZSB0ZXJuYXJ5IG9wZXJhdG9yIGlzIG1vc3RseSBkZWZpbmVkIHdpdGggd2hhdCBzeW1ib2wocyk/",
            "correct_answer": "Pzo=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Pz8=",
                "aWYgdGhlbg==",
                "Pw=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlIGZvbGxvd2luZyBsYW5ndWFnZXMgaXMgdXNlZCBhcyBhIHNjcmlwdGluZyBsYW5ndWFnZSBpbiB0aGUgVW5pdHkgM0QgZ2FtZSBlbmdpbmU/",
            "correct_answer": "QyM=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "SmF2YQ==",
                "Qysr",
                "T2JqZWN0aXZlLUM="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hhdCBkb2VzICJMQ0QiIHN0YW5kIGZvcj8=",
            "correct_answer": "TGlxdWlkIENyeXN0YWwgRGlzcGxheQ==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "TGFuZ3VhZ2UgQ29udHJvbCBEZXNpZ24=",
                "TGFzdCBDb21tb24gRGlmZmVyZW5jZQ==",
                "TG9uZyBDb250aW51b3VzIERlc2lnbg=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hhdCBkaWQgdGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGhlIFRvciBBbm9ueW1pdHkgTmV0d29yayBvcmlnbmlhbGx5IHN0YW5kIGZvcj8=",
            "correct_answer": "VGhlIE9uaW9uIFJvdXRlcg==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "VGhlIE9ubHkgUm91dGVy",
                "VGhlIE9yYW5nZSBSb3V0ZXI=",
                "VGhlIE9taW5vdXMgUm91dGVy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "SW4gQ1NTLCB3aGljaCBvZiB0aGVzZSB2YWx1ZXMgQ0FOTk9UIGJlIHVzZWQgd2l0aCB0aGUgInBvc2l0aW9uIiBwcm9wZXJ0eT8=",
            "correct_answer": "Y2VudGVy",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "c3RhdGlj",
                "YWJzb2x1dGU=",
                "cmVsYXRpdmU="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIG5hbWUgZ2l2ZW4gdG8gQW5kcm9pZCA0LjM/",
            "correct_answer": "SmVsbHkgQmVhbg==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "TG9sbGlwb3A=",
                "TnV0ZWxsYQ==",
                "RnJveW8="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "SW4gcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcsIHdoYXQgZG8geW91IGNhbGwgZnVuY3Rpb25zIHdpdGggdGhlIHNhbWUgbmFtZSBidXQgZGlmZmVyZW50IGltcGxlbWVudGF0aW9ucz8=",
            "correct_answer": "T3ZlcmxvYWRpbmc=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "T3ZlcnJpZGluZw==",
                "QWJzdHJhY3Rpbmc=",
                "SW5oZXJpdGluZw=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hlbiBkaWQgdGhlIG9ubGluZSBzdHJlYW1pbmcgc2VydmljZSAiTWl4ZXIiIGxhdW5jaD8=",
            "correct_answer": "MjAxNg==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "MjAxMw==",
                "MjAwOQ==",
                "MjAxMQ=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hhdCB3YXMgdGhlIGZpcnN0IEFuZHJvaWQgdmVyc2lvbiBzcGVjaWZpY2FsbHkgb3B0aW1pemVkIGZvciB0YWJsZXRzPw==",
            "correct_answer": "SG9uZXljb21i",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "RWNsYWly",
                "RnJveW8=",
                "TWFyc2htZWxsb3c="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "SW4gY29tcHV0aW5nIHRlcm1zLCB0eXBpY2FsbHkgd2hhdCBkb2VzIENMSSBzdGFuZCBmb3I/",
            "correct_answer": "Q29tbWFuZCBMaW5lIEludGVyZmFjZQ==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Q29tbW9uIExhbmd1YWdlIElucHV0",
                "Q29udHJvbCBMaW5lIEludGVyZmFjZQ==",
                "Q29tbW9uIExhbmd1YWdlIEludGVyZmFjZQ=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "VGhlIG5hbWUgb2YgdGVjaG5vbG9neSBjb21wYW55IEhQIHN0YW5kcyBmb3Igd2hhdD8=",
            "correct_answer": "SGV3bGV0dC1QYWNrYXJk",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "SG93YXJkIFBhY2ttYW5u",
                "SHVza2VyLVBvbGxvc2s=",
                "SGVsbG1hbi1Qb2hs"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "SG93IG1hbnkgY29yZXMgZG9lcyB0aGUgSW50ZWwgaTctNjk1MFggaGF2ZT8=",
            "correct_answer": "MTA=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "MTI=",
                "OA==",
                "NA=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hhdCBmaXZlIGxldHRlciB3b3JkIGlzIHRoZSBtb3R0byBvZiB0aGUgSUJNIENvbXB1dGVyIGNvbXBhbnk/",
            "correct_answer": "VGhpbms=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Q2xpY2s=",
                "TG9naWM=",
                "UGl4ZWw="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "SW4gdGhlIHNlcnZlciBob3N0aW5nIGluZHVzdHJ5IElhYVMgc3RhbmRzIGZvci4uLg==",
            "correct_answer": "SW5mcmFzdHJ1Y3R1cmUgYXMgYSBTZXJ2aWNl",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "SW50ZXJuZXQgYXMgYSBTZXJ2aWNl",
                "SW50ZXJuZXQgYW5kIGEgU2VydmVy",
                "SW5mcmFzdHJ1Y3R1cmUgYXMgYSBTZXJ2ZXI="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggaW50ZXJuZXQgY29tcGFueSBiZWdhbiBsaWZlIGFzIGFuIG9ubGluZSBib29rc3RvcmUgY2FsbGVkICdDYWRhYnJhJz8=",
            "correct_answer": "QW1hem9u",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "ZUJheQ==",
                "T3ZlcnN0b2Nr",
                "U2hvcGlmeQ=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "TnZpZGlhJ3MgaGVhZHF1YXJ0ZXJzIGFyZSBiYXNlZCBpbiB3aGljaCBTaWxpY29uIFZhbGxleSBjaXR5Pw==",
            "correct_answer": "U2FudGEgQ2xhcmE=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "UGFsbyBBbHRv",
                "Q3VwZXJ0aW5v",
                "TW91bnRhaW4gVmlldw=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hpbGUgQXBwbGUgd2FzIGZvcm1lZCBpbiBDYWxpZm9ybmlhLCBpbiB3aGljaCB3ZXN0ZXJuIHN0YXRlIHdhcyBNaWNyb3NvZnQgZm91bmRlZD8=",
            "correct_answer": "TmV3IE1leGljbw==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "V2FzaGluZ3Rvbg==",
                "Q29sb3JhZG8=",
                "QXJpem9uYQ=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2Ugd2FzIGRldmVsb3BlZCBieSBTdW4gTWljcm9zeXN0ZW1zIGluIDE5OTU/",
            "correct_answer": "SmF2YQ==",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "UHl0aG9u",
                "U29sYXJpcyBPUw==",
                "Qysr"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "VGhlIGNvbXB1dGVyIE9FTSBtYW51ZmFjdHVyZXIgQ2xldm8sIGtub3duIGZvciBpdHMgU2FnZXIgbm90ZWJvb2sgbGluZSwgaXMgYmFzZWQgaW4gd2hpY2ggY291bnRyeT8=",
            "correct_answer": "VGFpd2Fu",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "VW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcw==",
                "R2VybWFueQ==",
                "Q2hpbmEgKFBlb3BsZSdzIFJlcHVibGljIG9mKQ=="
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
            "difficulty": "bWVkaXVt",
            "category": "U2NpZW5jZTogQ29tcHV0ZXJz",
            "question": "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2VzIGlzIGEgbG93LWxldmVsIGxhbmd1YWdlPw==",
            "correct_answer": "QXNzZW1ibHk=",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "UHl0aG9u",
                "QyM=",
                "UGFzY2Fs"
            ]
        }
    ]
}